A very good afternoon friends we have box
with Anand set of questions and heavy art
of movie and welcome you are requested who neem
drive see for mission possible Singh Verma
Kasana and heavy art with new set of
questions or welcome you to ask question
oa 9:00 baj oil champions related to to that
jis hole kya peene se related to draw
Russian team Ruchi thanks and leaders want to
nahi so hai is of that question of the day khyat without question
of the day you can
participate and dars and business top 10
you can answer 10 question a viewers hai is the
question you are driving when you
notice smoke coming out of its own and
your Ragini arre means when you were driving and
you noticed that the dua hai vo
nikal se raftaar available boys investigate
stopenge open kareng board and
investigate knot bluetooth off  Let's go
now they will leave and you will wait
this user affair respiration tool and day
open the board you will use papyrus traditional tool in
then open your don't
chapatis political and run away you will park your side
and run away so here is
the question come join and answer it
and no but be a part of trust and you
can one more exciting prizes of uno
10,000 seventh day and have a third question
of the day too many questions are left and
big be a part of tata s well and you can
win this lack dikhai prize you are you can even when
multiplied commissioner to multiple
prizes will give you can
participate in all 5 questions and school
camp in Ujjain till the
accessibility key so January joint
benefit of every alarm you can be a part
of the stems editing c and I screen
grh question please gamlon with your family
and  Friends, I can also be part of
this and you can also form in the next
9 newsroom naturally questions
this note smoking coming out of which you
will stop in boys and girls and boys open
the button and run away what will you do now you are
watching this you have noticed that the prayer is
coming out of your blood that at that
time you will stop and
open your button and investigate you
will check what the problem is or what has
happened or you will get out of your mouth
and tagged you will get out of your mouth and
stand outside and wait or
use the first Indian to
alarm day open the button you first Indian
to use the web arm open your mouth
or PDF button and run away or do the
affair this and
run away from there so now tell me this
is very delicate and can happen to anyone at any time
so what will you do in such a situation
tell us and we have half a pitch chance to win
gifts  Antu these chicken knowledge
related to road safety the motive is put this
exams here next to make every
day for one together we can make main road se jaaye jaaye so
people like that
follow some rules and regulations previous nuvvu
we see here how
well people are trying to maintain distance between
and follow quickly if you can do it then
we can also do it you can also
make our Indian roads better we
also just got a request to subscribe
pims very important and similarly our
other questions are related to Arundhati
you have to participate in it
you have to tell
how good is your knowledge how much do you know about road safety
Rohit some relative
Siddheshwari important to information
people know about things we know
what things we should follow and what we should
not do what are the rules there are
regulations but are important fast how much
you follow friend setting on the road you
those things  How much do we follow the rules, the
answer to this question is no, most people say no,
and many such questions come,
we all know that we should
follow what is there in the city, we will finally
ask anyone in the Bigg Boss house,
first we will talk to anyone, so now if we
talk to even a small child, if we ask him,
brother, please
tell us something related to road safety, then he can also tell that
we should wear helmets, we should wear it at this time,
we should cross only from this rock crossing,
but the thing to think about is that
how much do we follow those things,
yes,
we are there too, then we have to bring change
within ourselves, we should
change those things, we have to take those things forward so that
we can change things and
make more members of our society, so that is why we request you that
please join us,
join it with your family, your friends, with the people
you love, with your love family
and be a part of this campaign
and help us, your nation  To
make it clean and safe because
somewhere or the other in everyone's life roses are
very important, somewhere or the other
you use roses on a daily basis, whether
you are going to marketing, going to
office, going to school,
from a small child to an adult, everyone is facing
problems, wherever you go, you have
contact with roses somewhere, roses are yours,
your sleep is in Delhi University, Delhi,
so
how can we make this so important for you, we all have to
see that together, so that's why Aghori camp in ghuslo
with now mission impossible drive
just ginger pipe semolina mission impossible try
then question screen editing see you are
driving mode off, have you noticed that the
prayer is coming out from the on, then
what will you do boys
investigate will come, open your and see
Shravan mystery click or get
out of there, then you will come out of the palace
and wait or user of
fire space traditional to alarm day open the don't  We will
use the festival tool
Andhra then we will take our donut or the lash
five time alarm runway you
will turn on your mic and you will run out of there,
so it is up to you to decide what
you will do in that thing you will
answer it you have 2 hours
after 2 hours our other anchor will
join you unveil new
questions new and huge dot you can
price that and
scan your wrist * otherwise kasha na thank you
for the day all the best
stay healthy tune in also on Monday